Are you okay?
大丈夫?
There's something scary about your face, man.
何か顔怖がってるよ、君
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Do you understand the meaning of this job?
このお仕事、意味わかってきたの?
Yes, maybe.
はい、多分
perhaps?
多分?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's an engineering part-time job.
工学バイトだよ
yes.
はい
I want money.
お金欲しくて
お金欲しいんだ
How old are you now?
君今何歳だっつってたっけ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18 years old?
18歳?
What are you doing kid?
何してる子?
I'm a student.
学生です
I need money.
お金必要なんだ
yes.
はい
Can't make it with a normal part-time job?
普通のバイトじゃ間に合わないの?
I want to buy a present for my boyfriend.
彼氏にプレゼント買いたくて
That's right.
そうなんだ
yes.
はい
Do you love it?
大好きなの?
Is it quite expensive?
結構高いものなの?
that.
それ
I agree.
そうですね
Actually, what do you do as an engineering part-time worker?
実際さ、工学バイトってどういうことやるか、
Did you anticipate something?
何 か、予想ついたりしてた?
I don't know.
わかんない
Don't you know?
わかんない?
An engineering part-time job is a lot of money that you wouldn't get from a normal part-time job.
工学バイトってのは、 普通のアルバイトじゃ貰えないぐらいの金
A job where you can earn a large amount of money in a short amount of time.
額 を、 短時間で稼ぐ仕事
I do some pretty hard things.
結構ハードなことするんだよ
yes.
はい
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You have a beautiful body.
君、体きれいだね
You have great skin.
すごい良いお肌してるね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Do you usually take care of yourself?
普段何かケアとかしてるの?
especially.
特に
I don't really do anything.
特にしてないんだ
It feels good to touch something.
何か触ったら気持ちよさそうだね
Is that so?
ですかね
Won't your boyfriend tell you that?
彼氏とかに言われないの?
When I'm having sex, it feels good when I touch something, etc.
エッチしてる時とかさ、 何か触ると気持ちいいんだけどとか、
Will you tell me?
言われるの?
Do you have a lot of sex with him?
結構エッチするの、彼と?
yes.
はい
Do it.
するんだ
Well then, you can do it.
じゃあ、できるね
I can do this part time job.
このバイトできるよ
Simply put, all you have to do is have sex.
簡単に言ったら、 エッチすればいいだけ
Not just having sex, but having sex in front of the camera
ただエッチするだけじゃなくて、 カメラの前でエッチするんだ
But that's not to say I'm just kidding,
けど、 それは別に、 う ったりとかするんじゃなくて、
That's simply what I did,
単純に、 そういう仕事をしましたよ、
That's it.
って
That's all the evidence, like a video evidence.
それだけの証拠、 証拠動画みたいな感じ
Isn't it safe?
安心でしょ?
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
Your hands are sweaty, aren't they?
手に汗かいてるじゃない?
stop?
やめる?
Are you going to quit?
やめちゃう?
So, shall we go home?
じゃあ、帰る?
I can't buy him a present?
彼にプレゼント買えないよ?
Isn't it dull?
くすらりだでしょ?
Well then, let's do our best.
じゃあ、頑張ってやろうか
I want to see your underwear today.
君のさ、 今日の下着見たいんだけど、
Can I have you roll up that sweater like this?
こうやってさ、 そのセーター巻くってもらってもいい?
Like this.
こうやって
I'll call some staff.
ちょっとスタッフ呼ぶよ
again.
改めて
She's a hairy girl.
毛の毛な彼女だね
Nice, you.
いいね、君
Let's take off the sweater.
セーター脱いちゃおうよ
I can't see your pants with this.
これじゃあ、 パンツ見えないね
These are pants, right?
これパンツでしょ?
Hey, it's not a skirt.
ねえ、スカートじゃないよね
I like the style.
スタイルいいね
Do you play any sports?
なんかスポーツとかやってんの?
Haven't you done it?
やって ない?
You're doing a great job.
よっぱいしてるね
Look at everything.
全部見して
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
That's right.
そうなんだ
Bend that arm.
そっちの腕曲げて
Cross your knees.
両膝組んで
Isn't the style nice?
スタイルいいじゃない?
Just like that.
そのまま
Turn around and keep your arms up.
両腕上げたまま、 後ろ向いてみて
That's amazing.
すごいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
My thighs are now tucked in, though.
内股になっちゃってるけどね
Don't you want to stand up?
立ってらんない?
TRUE?
本当?
The more you show me, the more I'll get excited.
いっぱい見せてくれたら、その分弾むよ
Socks were a keeper.
靴下はキーパーだったね
It's wet.
濡れてるじゃん
Aren't you wet?
濡れてない?
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's a mess, man.
ぐちゃぐちゃだよ、君
look?
見る?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
It's soaking wet.
びっしょびしょだよ
look?
見る?
You'll see it, right?
見るでしょ?
Will you cry?
涙くれる?
That's what you're doing for me, right?
そういうことしてあげてるんでしょ、
Even my boyfriend.
彼氏にも
You really like it, don't you?
めっちゃ好きでしょ?
You say it's chewy a lot, right?
もっちりっていっぱい言ってるでしょ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
This is what's standing over here.
こっちひら立ってるもん、これ
Are you asleep?
寝 ちゃってる?
Maybe.
もしかして
Assemble it above, like this.
上で組んでて、こうやって
I've been putting it all together at the top, and that's it.
ずっと上で組んでて、それ
What should I do with this?
こんなんどうしちゃうよ
What should I do?
どうしちゃう?
why?
なんで?
Well, I just stood up.
なんかさ、立っちゃったもん、さ
Well, but.
で、だけどさ
Because it felt good.
気持ちよかったから
When you remember, remember.
思い出したら、思い出し立ち
Remembering.
思い出し立ち
why?
なんで?
Let's try again.
もう一回しよう
It's become like this.
こんなになってるじゃん
Right?
でしょ?
why?
なんで?
Do you hate hard things?
固いの嫌い?
Look.
ほら
Chin-chin, let me go.
ちんちん、離してくれ
It's slimy now.
今、ぬるっとしてるんだよ
crying
泣
If there's a way, I'll definitely go in.
き 方があったら、入っちゃう、絶対
Isn't your clitoris getting bigger?
クリトリス、大きくなってないの?
Isn't it getting bigger?
大きくなってないの?
lie?
嘘?
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってるよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
My clitoris is getting swollen.
クリトリス、パンパンになってる
Hasn't it happened?
なってない?
That's a lie.
嘘だよ
Don't like it the second time?
2回目嫌?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃないでしょ
Don't hate it
嫌じゃないで
Sho.
しょ
why?
なん で?
what?
何?
It's not your clitoris, so let me tap it.
クリトリスじゃないんだから、タップしてもらおう
Stop each other?
止め合いを?
No?
ダメ?
why?
なんで?
It's wet though.
濡れてるんだけど
Aren't you wet?
濡れてない?
lie?
嘘?
I got wet.
濡れたよ
Go, go, go.
行く、行く、行く
The second shot also came out.
2発目も出てきたよ
Session news.
セッショニュース